preventnow.com 2017-03-13

# Privacy Policy | Omada

* * *

### Privacy Policy (United States)

Omada Health, Inc. (the “Company”) knows that you care about how your personal information is collected, used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. By visiting the [go.omadahealth.com](https://go.omadahealth.com/) website and domain name (and the other websites we own or operate, including, without limitation, [www.omadahealth.com](https://www.omadahealth.com/)) and any other linked pages, features, content, or related services offered from time to time by the Company in connection therewith (collectively, the “Site” as further defined in our Terms of Use (“Terms”)), using our mobile application (the “Mobile App”) or using any of our Services, you consent to this Privacy Policy and to our use and processing of Personal Information for the purposes set forth herein. Capitalized terms not defined in this Privacy Policy shall have the meanings set forth in our Terms, available at [go.omadahealth.com/terms-of-use](https://go.omadahealth.com/terms-of-use).

“Company” or the terms “we” or “us” or similar terms refer to Omada Health, Inc. “You” or “your” or similar terms refer to you as a user of our Services.

By accepting our Privacy Policy during registration, or by visiting and/or using the Site, the Mobile App or any of our Services, you (a) expressly consent to our collection, use, disclosure and processing of your Personal Information (as defined below) in accordance with this Privacy Policy, and (b) expressly acknowledge that you have read and understood our HIPAA Notice, which describes how we may use and disclose health information about you for treatment, payment or health care operations and for other purposes that are permitted or required by law, including the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act of 1996, as amended from time to time (“HIPAA”). Our HIPAA Notice is available at [go.omadahealth.com/hipaa](https://go.omadahealth.com/hipaa). Any conflict between this Privacy Policy and the HIPAA Notice with respect to any PHI (as defined in the HIPAA Notice) shall be governed by the HIPAA Notice.

As used in this Privacy Policy, the terms “using” and “processing” information include, among other things, using cookies or embedded scripts on a computer, browser, laptop, tablet, mobile phone or other device (a “Device”), subjecting the information to statistical or other analysis, and using or handling information in any way, including without limitation collecting, storing, evaluating, modifying, deleting, using, combining, disclosing, and transferring information within our organization or among our affiliates within the United States or internationally, as well as using personal information to respond to user / applicant or sponsor (i.e., the entity or organization paying for your participation in our Services) requests and to provide the requested products and services.

#### 1\. WHAT DOES THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVER?

Personal Information – In General.

This Privacy Policy covers how we use and disclose personally identifiable information that we gather from you starting from the time that you initially access our Site, our Mobile App or use our Services. Personally identifiable information refers to any information about you that can be used to contact or identify you and information on your use or potential use of the Site, our Mobile App or our Services, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a personal profile, an email address or other contact information (collectively, “Personal Information”). Your privacy is important to us, and we are committed to carefully managing your Personal Information in connection with the Services that we provide. It is important for you to understand, however, that this policy does not apply to the practices of companies and / or websites or other third party services that we do not own or control, or to individuals that we do not employ or manage.

Protected Health Information.

We are dedicated to maintaining the privacy and integrity of protected health information that we receive as part of your application for or participation in the our Services (“PHI”). PHI is Personal) Information that we receive as part of your application for or participation in the our program that relates to (a) your past, present, or future physical or mental health or condition, (b) the provision of health care to you, or (c) your past, present, or future payment for the provision of health care, which is created, received, transmitted, or maintained by the Company. This Privacy Policy describes how we protect your privacy as a visitor to, or general user of our Site, our Mobile App and Services. You have additional rights under federal and state law with respect to the access to, use, and disclosure of Personal Information that constitutes PHI. For a more complete description of your rights with respect to PHI, please refer to our HIPAA Notice, which provides important information to you about how we may use and disclose your PHI. Our HIPAA Notice is available here: [go.omadahealth.com/hipaa](https://go.omadahealth.com/hipaa)

#### 2\. WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

We collect Personal Information you choose to provide us (e.g., through registrations, applications, use of the Services, surveys, and in connection with your inquiries), starting from the time that you initially access our Site, our Mobile App or use our Services. The information we gather from you enables us to administer your account, provide you with the Services, respond to your inquiries and send you communications regarding the Services and your access to and use of the same, obtain your feedback on our Site, our Mobile App and our Services, analyze user behavior and activity, personalize and improve our Services, conduct research activities and contact you about the services that we offer.

From time to time, we may use or augment the Personal Information we have about you with information obtained from third parties (e.g., FitBit or Apple). For example, we may use such third party information to confirm contact or financial information, to verify eligibility, or to better understand your interests by associating demographic information with the information you have provided.

We collect the following types of information:

Personal Information You Provide to Us.

We receive and store any information you enter on our Site, our Mobile App or provide to us through the Services, including any third party services that you connect with our Services (e.g., FitBit or Apple). Personal Information that we collect may include things like your full name, gender, mobile phone number, credit card and/or other payment information (if applicable – i.e., self-pay participants), your email address and the email address of your contacts, home and business postal addresses, IP address, browser information, username, password, certain health information (e.g., height, weight, blood pressure, blood glucose, pre-existing medical conditions, tracking of food, sleep and/or activity and insurance information), and any other information or data that you provide when using our Site, our Mobile App and/or our Services. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but that may result in our inability to provide you access to or use of many of our special features. Omada’s goal is to use the Personal Information you provide for such purposes as answering questions and communicating with you about the Company’s products and services, including updates and new features.

PLEASE NOTE: By using the Services, you consent to and authorize Omada to disclose your eligibility for and participation in the Services (i.e., you meet the clinical enrollment criteria for the Services, which may identify those individuals at risk for certain chronic diseases or living with certain chronic diseases and have elected at your own discretion to participate in the same) to the other users of the Site, the Mobile App and the Services. The users, including but not limited to administrators, health coaches and other authorized Omada personnel, and your fellow support group members will have access to a range of Personal Information such as your user name and picture, linking you to your diagnosis and/or reason for program participation. Moreover, as we group participants based on certain characteristics, fellow support group members may be co-workers or other acquaintances.

We take great efforts in protecting your privacy; however, we cannot control, and expressly disclaim any responsibility for, whether or how users will subsequently use or disclose posted or previously disclosed information. If you do not consent to the disclosure of this information, you should not access or use the Site, the Mobile App or the Services. The Services include the ability for users to share Personal Information, including information regarding your medical condition. Any information you choose to provide or upload to the group Sites or the Mobile App, including Personal Information about your medical condition, will be visible to your group, as well as health coaches, administrators, and other users. As your information will be viewable to the other users of the Site, the Mobile App and the Services, you should provide only the information you feel comfortable disclosing. There may be an opportunity to speak on the phone or via video chat in a group conference call. Participation in such opportunities is not mandatory, but should you choose to participate, you should share only as much information as you feel comfortable sharing in these additional forums.

Personal Information Collected Automatically.

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with the Site, the Mobile App and / or use the Services. We automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, and the page you requested. In addition, we may use personal identifiers to recognize you when you arrive at the Site via an external link, such as a link appearing on a third party site or in an Omada-generated email presented to you. See also our What About Tracking Technologies? section below. We will also use your information to provide customer service and support.

Generally, our Services automatically collect usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to the Site and Mobile App and its components, similar to TV ratings that indicate how many people watched a particular show. We only use this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, and not in a manner that would permit us to identify you personally (“De-identified Information”). This type of aggregate data enables us to figure out how often users or customers use parts of the Site, Mobile App or Services so that we can make the Site, Mobile App and Services as appealing to as many users and customers as possible and improve our Services. We may provide this de-identified, aggregate data to our partners and/or customers to identify how our users use our Site, Mobile App and/or Services. Again, we never disclose information to a partner or customer in a manner that would identify you personally.

You may set your browser to refuse or disable these data collection methods, but doing so may change your experience with the Site, the Mobile App or the Services, diminish certain aspects of the Site’s or Mobile App’s functionality or render certain features of the Site, the Mobile App or the Services inoperable. The Site may not recognize or respond to “do not track” technologies employed by your browser.

E-mail Communications.

We often receive a confirmation when you open an email from us if your computer supports this type of program. We use this confirmation to help us make emails more interesting and helpful. We also compare our customer list to lists received from other companies in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our customers. When you receive e-mail from us, you can opt out of receiving further e-mails by following the included instructions to unsubscribe. However, by opting out of further email communications after you enroll in the Services, you may limit program reminders and other valuable program content and components.

What About Tracking Technologies?

In addition to any Personal Information or other information that you choose to submit to us via the Site, Mobile App or Services, we and our third party service providers may use a variety of technologies that automatically (or passively) store or collect certain information when you visit or interact with the Site, Mobile App or Services (“Usage Information”). This Usage Information may be stored or accessed using technologies that may be downloaded to your Device whenever you visit or interact with the Site, Mobile App or Services. To the extent we associate Usage Information with your Personal Information that we collect directly from you, we will treat it as Personal Information. Examples of Usage Information include: your IP address or other unique device identifier (e.g., a number that is automatically assigned to your Device used to access the Site which our computers use to identify your Device), your Device’s functionality (e.g., browser, operating system, mobile network information, etc.), the areas within the Site or Services that you visit and your activities there, your Device location, your Device characteristics and certain other data regarding your Device.

We may use various methods or technologies to store or collect your Usage Information, including your visits to or interactions with our Site, Mobile App and Services (“Tracking Technologies”). We may use these Tracking Technologies for a variety of purposes, including but not limited to uses deemed to be necessary or useful to assess the performance of our Site, Mobile App and Services (including as part of our analytic practices or otherwise to improve our Site, Mobile App and Services) or uses required to offer you enhanced functionality when accessing our Site, Mobile App and Services (including identifying you when you sign in to the Site or the Mobile App or keeping track of your specified preferences).

Tracking Technologies that may include the following (and may include subsequent technologies and methods later developed which perform a similar function):

Cookies. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our Site are visited and by how many people. We use cookies to enhance visitors’ experiences by understanding how visitors and / or users engage with and navigate our Site. Regular cookies may generally be disabled or removed by tools that are available as part of most commercial browsers and in some but not all instances can be blocked in the future by selecting certain settings. Each browser that you use will need to be set separately, and different browsers offer different functionality and options in this regard. Also, these tools may not be effective with regard to certain types of cookies (e.g., Adobe Flash or HTML5 cookies). Please be aware that if you disable or remove cookies on your Device, some parts of our Site or Services may not function properly and when you revisit our Site or Services your ability to limit cookies is subject to your browser settings and limitations.

We may choose to serve ads on the Site or the Mobile App. These ads may be delivered to users by our advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your Device each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy refers only to the use of cookies by the Company and does not cover the use of cookies by any third parties (e.g., advertisers).

Embedded Scripts. An embedded script is programming code that is designed to collect information about your interactions with the Site, Mobile App and Services, such as the links that you click on. The code is temporarily downloaded onto your Device, is active only while you are connected to the Site or Mobile App, and is deactivated or deleted thereafter.

Web Beacons. Small graphic images or other web programming code called “web beacons” (also known as “1×1 GIFs” or “clear GIFs”) may be included in pages and messages of our Site, Mobile App and Services. Web beacons may be invisible to you, but any electronic image or other web programming code inserted into a page or e-mail can act as a web beacon. Web beacons or similar technologies may be used for a number of purposes, including to count visitors to the Site, Mobile App and Services, to monitor how users navigate the Site, the Mobile App and Services, to count how many sent e-mails were actually opened or to count how many particular articles or links were actually viewed.

There may be other Tracking Technologies now and later devised and used by us in connection with the Site, Mobile App and Services. Further, third parties may use Tracking Technologies with our Website. We do not control those Tracking Technologies, and we are not responsible for them. However, you consent to potentially encountering third party Tracking Technologies in connection with your use of the Site and Services and accept that this Privacy Policy does not apply to the Tracking Technologies or practices of such third parties. In such cases, you must check the third party websites to confirm how your information is collected and used.

#### 3\. WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE SHARE?

Personal Information regarding our users is an integral part of our business. We will not rent, sell or share your Personal Information with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide the Services, when we otherwise have your permission, as expressly permitted or required by the HIPAA Notice or as expressly permitted or required under this Privacy Policy, including under the following circumstances:

Forums: We may make available your Personal Information through the Site, the Mobile App and/or the Services (for example, discussion boards, chat rooms, profile pages, bulletin boards, blogs, instant messaging, activities, polls, games and other communication forums) (each, a “Forum”) to which you post information and materials. Some of these Forums are described more specifically below. Please note that any information, text, and images posted or disclosed by the user on or through such Forums may be visible to the user’s group(s), as well as our health coaches and other authorized personnel, administrators, visitors to the Site or the Mobile App, and other users of the Site or the Mobile App. Specifically, Personal Information such as the picture you’ve uploaded and your screen name may be available for other users to view when you make a posting to such Forums. Information regarding your activities in such Services may also be available for view by other users. (For example, other users may be able to view a list of all postings you have made in all available Forums.) Any postings you have made to a Forum may also be available for view later by users of the Site or the Mobile App by scrolling to older posts on the Forum. We urge you to exercise discretion and caution when deciding to disclose your Personal Information, such as your health information, or any other information, through a Forum or otherwise through the Site.

Discussion Boards and Chat Rooms: We may provide functionality to post on our discussion boards, and permit you to enter into chat rooms and communicate with other users in the chat rooms. Please note that if you use such functionalities to communicate, your name / screen name will be disclosed to all visitors to the discussion boards, present and future, as well as all users in the chat room at that time. Please remember that information posted to discussion boards becomes public information. Use caution when posting. Further, if a comment you make on the discussion board or in the chat room contains Personal Information, we cannot control how the Personal Information will be used or disclosed by the other users of the discussion board or chat room. We urge you to exercise discretion and caution when deciding to disclose your Personal Information, or any other information, in any comment and/or message, and to be careful about the people to whom you send such comments and/or messages.

Messaging Services: We may provide functionality to permit you to send messages, including instant messages, to other users through the Site. Please note that if you use such functionality to send such a message to another user, your screen name will be disclosed to that user, as well as administrators. Further, if a message you send using such functionality contains Personal Information, we cannot control how the Personal Information will be used or disclosed by the recipient of your message. We urge you to exercise discretion and caution when deciding to disclose your Personal Information, or any other information, in any message, and to be careful about the people to whom you send such messages.

IN THE CASE OF YOUR USE OF FORUMS, DISCUSSION BOARDS, CHAT ROOMS AND MESSAGING SERVICES, AS DESCRIBED ABOVE, WE ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE USE BY OTHERS OF ANY INFORMATION, INCLDUING PERSONAL INFORMATION, THAT IS DISCLOSED BY YOU OR ON YOUR BEHALF BY YOUR SYSTEM IN SUCH FORUMS, DISCUSSION BOARDS, CHAT ROOMS AND MESSAGING SERVICES. BY DISCLOSING ANY OF YOUR INFORMATION VIA FORUMS, DISCUSSION BOARDS, CHAT ROOMS AND MESSAGING SERVICES, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND ACCEPT ANY RISK AND DAMAGE ARISING FROM DISCLOSURE OF SUCH INFORMATION.

User Profiles: We may provide functionality to permit you to create a user profile page in which you may provide information about yourself, including, without limitation, your health information, symptoms, treatments, as well as your feelings about your health information and/or yourself (“User Submissions,” as further defined in our Terms). You may also be able to upload pictures, videos and stories to your profile page as part of the User Submissions. User Submissions may be displayed to other users (including members of your group(s), who may be from the same deployment or otherwise affiliated) to facilitate user interaction within the Services. Email addresses are used to add new User Submissions to user profiles and to communicate through User Submissions. Users’ email addresses will not be directly revealed to other users by us, except when the user is “connected” to another user via a shared group membership, or an invitation, or if the user has chosen to include their email address in their User Profile. Please note that any User Submissions you make, including Personal Information, on or through your profile page may be available for other users, the Company, administration, moderators, and other staff. Additionally, other users may be able to post comments and view posted comments on your profile page.

Communication in Response to User Submissions: As part of the Site and Services, you will receive from us email and other communication relating to your User Submissions. You acknowledge and agree that by posting such User Submissions, we may send you email and other communications (e.g., phone calls or text messages) that we determine, in our sole discretion, are related to your User Submissions.

Affiliated Businesses We Do Not Control: In order to provide you with the optimal user experience, we anticipate that we may become affiliated and work closely with a variety of third party businesses. In certain situations, these businesses may sell products or services to you through the Sites. In other situations, we may provide services, or sell products, jointly with affiliated businesses. You should be able to recognize when an affiliated business is associated with your transactions, and throughout the course of the transactions, we will share your Personal Information that is related to such transactions with that affiliated business.

Agents: We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products and/or services to you. Without specific authorization and/or consent, we limit the rights of our agents to use Personal Information we share with them to that which is minimally necessary to assist us. You hereby consent to our sharing of Personal Information for the above purposes.

Referrals: From time to time, we may ask or invite you to refer our Services to family members, colleagues or friends. In these cases, it is your responsibility to ensure that these persons are indeed family members (marriage, common-law partnership or parent-child relationship) or people with whom you have a personal relationship (frequency of communication, sharing of interests, opinions, etc.). In short, we ask you to limit your invitations to people in your inner circle that may have an interest in our Services. We will send them an email saying that you have suggested that they may be interested to try our Services. We will not contact them again if they do not reply or if they request that we do not contact them again.

Promotional Offers: We will never disclose your personal information to other businesses for their marketing purposes, but we may send you offers that promote the products of other businesses. These offers will be intended to benefit you, your health, or your Omada experience. If you do not wish to receive these offers, you can click the “unsubscribe” link contained within the emails or you can send an email with your request to [privacy@omadahealth.com](mailto:privacy@omadahealth.com). We will process your request within a reasonable time, but you may receive additional offers as we process your request.

Business Transfers: In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information, including Personal Information about customers, is typically one of the business assets that are transferred. Moreover, if the Company, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that the Company goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, Personal Information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. By continuing to use the Site, the Mobile App and Services, you acknowledge that if we sell or transfer our business (e.g., through an acquisition) or an asset (e.g., our website) to another company, we will share your personal information with such company and will require such company to use and protect your personal information consistent with this Privacy Policy.

Sponsors and Third Party Administrators; As Required by Law: We may, in our sole discretion, share, transfer or otherwise disclose certain of your Personal Information (e.g., reports containing data related to enrollment, engagement, retention, and outcomes) to your sponsor or your sponsor’s third party administrators (e.g., incentives vendors, wellness administrators, etc.) for treatment, payment, or healthcare operations purposes and for other purposes permitted or required by law, as more fully described in our HIPAA Notice.

Protection of the Company and Others: We may release Personal Information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with the law; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of the Company, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection, detection or suppression, and credit risk reduction. If necessary, we will make all legally required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your Personal Information, including, without limitation, breaches of your unencrypted, electronically stored “personal information” or “medical information” (as defined in applicable state statutes on security breach notification). To the extent permitted by applicable laws, we will make such disclosures to you via email or conspicuous posting on your private profile on the Site or the Mobile App in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, insofar as consistent with (a) the legitimate needs of law enforcement, or (b) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system.

With Your Consent: Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your Personal Information may be shared with third parties, and will be able to control the sharing of this information.

De-identified Information: We may create De-Identified Information from the information that you share with us, including any Personal Information, and use such De-identified Information without restriction. We may, for example, share De-identified Information with the sponsors paying for your participation in the Services (e.g., reports containing data related to enrollment, engagement, retention, and outcomes to evidence overall program success metrics) and with third party administrators working with the sponsors to administer certain services to you (e.g., incentives vendors, wellness administrators, etc.). Again, we never disclose aggregate information in a manner that would identify you personally.

#### 4\. IS MY PERSONAL INFORMATION SECURE?

We employ industry standard administrative, physical, and technical measures designed to safeguard and protect information under our control from unauthorized access, use, and disclosure. In addition, when we collect, maintain, access, use, or disclose your Personal Information, we will do so using systems and processes consistent with information privacy and security requirements under applicable federal and state laws, including, without limitation, HIPAA.

Furthermore, your individual user account is protected by a password for your privacy and security. To ensure that there is no unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information, we suggest that you safeguard your password appropriately and limit access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account.

The Site and the Mobile App contain links to third party websites (“Third Party Websites”). In such an event, before using the Third Party Websites or related services, you must review and accept the terms of use and privacy policies for those sites and/or services. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices of any Third Party Websites, and we are not responsible or liable for the availability, reliability, content, functions, performance, accuracy, legality, appropriateness, services, materials, or any other aspect of such Third Party Websites. This Privacy Policy only governs information collected on our Site, our Mobile App or through our Services. When you access any Third Party Websites, you do so at your own risk, and you understand and agree that you are solely responsible for reading and understanding any terms of use and/or privacy policies that apply to such Third Party Wbsites.

We exercise great care to protect your personal information. However, we cannot ensure or warrant the security and confidentiality of any information that you transmit to us or receive from us via the Services offered through our Site and Mobile App, by Internet or wireless connection, including email, or the appropriateness of the measures we use to safeguard such information. Unauthorized entry, access, or use; loss; hardware or software failure; and other factors, may compromise the security of your information at any time. This is especially true for any information that you transmit to us via email or text message, since we have no way of protecting that information until it reaches us. E-mail and text message and the communication lines they travel over do not have the security features that are built into our Site and Mobile App and may not be secure. In addition, by downloading the Mobile App from a digital distribution platform such as the Apple App Store or Google Play (a “Mobile App Provider”), the Mobile App Provider and its agents may be able to identify you as a user of our Services. If you have reason to believe that your data or your interactions with us are no longer secure, you may contact us at the email address, mailing address or telephone number listed at the end of this Privacy Policy. In addition, if you have privacy or data security related questions, please feel free to contact the office identified at the end of this Privacy Policy.

#### 5\. WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION CAN I ACCESS AND CORRECT?

You can access certain information about you for the purpose of viewing, and in certain situations, updating that information. This list may change as the Site and Services change.

  * Real name
  * Account and user profile information (e.g., nickname and picture)
  * User email address
  * User mailing address
  * User mobile phone number
  * Username and password
  * Communication preferences

In order to help us maintain and ensure that your information is accurate and up to date, please update your information if it changes or inform us promptly at [support@omadahealth.com](mailto:support@omadahealth.com) so that we make the appropriate changes.

#### 6\. WHAT CHOICES DO I HAVE REGARDING MY PERSONAL INFORMATION?

As stated previously, you can always opt not to disclose information, even though it may be needed to take advantage of certain features of the Site, the Mobile App and the Services.

You are able to add or update certain information on pages, such as those listed in the “What Personal Information Can I Access And Correct” section, above. When you update information, however, we often maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records.

If you would like us to remove your records from our system, you may request deletion of your account with us by sending e-mail to [privacy@omadahealth.com](mailto:privacy@omadahealth.com). Please note that some information may remain in our records after deletion of your account, including any information or records we are legally obligated to retain. We will process your request within a reasonable time, but please note that you may receive additional communications and offers as we process your request.

If you do not wish to receive email or other mail, phone calls or texts from us, please click on the “Unsubscribe” link contained in the emails or indicate this preference by emailing us at [privacy@omadahealth.com](mailto:privacy@omadahealth.com). Please note that if you do not want to receive legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Policy, those legal notices will still govern your use of the Site, Mobile App and Services, and you are responsible for reviewing such legal notices for changes. We will process your request within a reasonable time, but please note that you may receive additional emails as we process your request.

#### 7\. HOW DO WE PROTECT CHILDREN’S PERSONAL INFORMATION?

The Services are not directed to children. We do not knowingly allow or solicit anyone under the age of 18 to participate independently in any of the Services. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us. If we become aware that a user of the Services is under the age of 18 and has provided us with Personal Information without verifiable parental consent, we will delete such Personal Information from our files.

#### 8\. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

By using the Site, Mobile App and Services, you agree to the current Privacy Policy and our Terms, into which this Privacy Policy is incorporated. We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to modify, discontinue, or terminate the Services or to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used or disclosed. If we make changes in the way we use Personal Information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our Site and/or sending you an email. By continuing to access or use the Services after we have posted a modification or have provided you with notice of a modification, you are indicating that you agree to be bound by the modified Privacy Policy. If the modified Privacy Policy is not acceptable to you, your only recourse is to cease accessing the Site or Mobile App and using the Services.

#### 9\. QUESTIONS OR CONCERNS

If you have any questions, concerns or complaints regarding privacy on our Site or Mobile App or if you want to make a request to access or correct your Personal Information, please contact our Privacy Officer at:

By email: [privacy@omadahealth.com](mailto:privacy@omadahealth.com)

By mail:  
Privacy Officer  
Omada Health, Inc.  
500 Sansome St., Suite 200  
San Francisco, CA 94111

By phone: 415.484.7050

We will make every effort to respond to your questions, concerns complaints and requests within a reasonable time.

Effective Date: February 1, 2017

* * *

### Política de privacidad (Estados Unidos)

Omada Health, Inc. (la “Empresa”) sabe que a usted le preocupa cómo se recopila, utiliza y comparte su información personal y nos tomamos muy en serio su privacidad. Al ingresar a la página web y al nombre de dominio [go.omadahealth.com](https://go.omadahealth.com/) (y los otros sitios web de nuestra propiedad o que operamos, incluido, a título ilustrativo, [www.omadahealth.com](https://www.omadahealth.com/)) y a cualquier otra página vinculada, característica, contenido o servicios relacionados ofrecidos oportunamente por la Empresa en relación con ellos (conjuntamente, el “Sitio”, tal como se definen en nuestras Condiciones de Uso [“Condiciones”]), al usar nuestra aplicación móvil (la “Aplicación Móvil”) o al usar cualquiera de nuestros Servicios, usted acepta la presente Política de Privacidad y nuestro uso y procesamiento de la Información Personal con los fines establecidos en la presente Política. Los términos en mayúsculas no definidos en la presente Política de Privacidad tendrán los significados establecidos en nuestras Condiciones, disponibles en [go.omadahealth.com/terms-of-use](https://go.omadahealth.com/terms-of-use).

Los términos “Empresa” o “nosotros” o términos similares se refieren a Omada Health, Inc. “Usted” o “su” o términos similares se refieren a usted como usuario de nuestros Servicios.

Al aceptar nuestra Política de Privacidad durante el registro o al utilizar o ingresar al Sitio, a la Aplicación Móvil o a cualquiera de nuestros Servicios, usted (a) presta expresamente su consentimiento para que recolectemos, utilicemos, divulguemos y procesemos su Información Personal (tal como se define a continuación) en conformidad con la presente Política de Privacidad y (b) reconoce expresamente que ha leído y comprendido nuestra Notificación de HIPAA [Ley de Transferencia y Responsabilidad de Seguros Médicos], que describe cómo podríamos utilizar y divulgar información médica acerca de usted para operaciones de tratamiento, pago o atención médica, o con otros fines que permita o exija la ley, incluida la Ley de Transferencia y Responsabilidad de Seguros Médicos de 1996, con sus ocasionales enmiendas (“HIPAA”). Nuestra Notificación de HIPAA se encuentra disponible en [go.omadahealth.com/hipaa](https://go.omadahealth.com/hipaa). Todo conflicto entre la presente Política de Privacidad y la Notificación de HIPAA respecto de cualquier IMP (según se define en la Notificación de HIPAA) quedará sujeto a la Notificación de HIPAA.

Tal como se utilizan en la presente Política de Privacidad, los términos “uso” y “procesamiento” de información incluyen, entre otras acciones, el uso de cookies o scripts incrustados en una computadora, navegador, laptop, tablet, teléfono celular u otro dispositivo (un “Dispositivo”), el sometimiento de información a análisis estadísticos u otros, y el uso o la manipulación de información de cualquier manera, inclusive, a título enunciativo y no limitativo, la recolección, almacenamiento, evaluación, modificación, eliminación, uso, combinación, divulgación y transferencia de información dentro de nuestra organización o entre nuestros afiliados dentro de los Estados Unidos o a nivel internacional, así como el uso de información personal para responder a solicitudes de usuarios/ solicitantes o patrocinadores (es decir, la entidad u organización que paga para que usted participe en nuestros Servicios) y para brindar los productos y los servicios solicitados.

#### 1\. ¿CUÁL ES EL ALCANCE DE LA PRESENTE POLÍTICA DE PRIVACIDAD?

Información personal en general

La presente Política de Privacidad abarca la manera en que utilizamos y divulgamos la información de identificación personal que recolectamos de usted desde el momento en que usted accede por primera vez a nuestros Sitio o Aplicación Móvil, o utiliza nuestros Servicios. La información de identificación personal se refiere a información acerca de usted que puede utilizarse para comunicarse con usted o identificarlo, e información sobre su uso o uso potencial del Sitio, de nuestra Aplicación Móvil o de nuestros Servicios, incluidos, a título ilustrativo, un nombre y apellido, un perfil personal, una dirección de correo electrónico u otra información de contacto (conjuntamente, “Información personal”). Su privacidad es importante para nosotros, y hemos asumido el compromiso de manejar atentamente su Información Personal en relación con los Servicios que prestamos. No obstante, es importante que comprenda que la presente política no se aplica a las prácticas de empresas o sitios web u otros servicios de terceros que no sean de nuestra propiedad o que no controlemos, ni a individuos que no empleemos ni dirijamos.

Información médica protegida

Nos comprometemos a mantener la privacidad y la integridad de la información médica protegida que recibimos de usted como parte de su solicitud para nuestros Servicios o su participación en ellos (“IMP”). La IMP es la Información Personal que recibimos de usted como parte de su solicitud para nuestro programa o participación en él, en relación con (a) su salud o estado físico o mental pasado, presente o futuro, (b) la atención médica que le sea brindada, o (c) sus pagos pasados, presentes o futuros por el suministro de atención médica creada, recibida, transmitida o mantenida por la Empresa. La presente Política de Privacidad describe la manera en que protegemos su privacidad como visitante o usuario general de nuestro Sitio, Aplicación Móvil y Servicios. Usted tiene derechos adicionales conforme a las leyes federales y estaduales con respecto al acceso, uso y divulgación de Información Personal que constituye IMP. Para obtener una descripción más completa de sus derechos respecto de la IMP, refiérase a nuestra Notificación de HIPAA, que le brinda información importante acerca de cómo podríamos utilizar y divulgar su IMP. Nuestra Notificación de HIPAA se encuentra disponible aquí: [go.omadahealth.com/hipaa](https://go.omadahealth.com/hipaa)

#### 2\. ¿QUÉ INFORMACIÓN PERSONAL RECOLECTAMOS?

Recolectamos la Información Personal que usted decide brindarnos (por ejemplo, a través de registros, aplicaciones, uso de los Servicios y encuestas y en relación con sus consultas) desde el momento en que accede a nuestro Sitio o Aplicación Móvil o utiliza nuestros Servicios por primera vez. La información que recolectamos de usted nos permite administrar su cuenta, prestarle los Servicios, responder a sus consultas y enviarle comunicaciones acerca de los Servicios y su uso y acceso a ellos, obtener sus comentarios acerca de nuestro Sitio, Aplicación Móvil y Servicios, analizar el comportamiento y la actividad del usuario, personalizar y mejorar nuestros Servicios, llevar a cabo actividades de investigación y comunicarnos con usted acerca de los servicios que ofrecemos.

Ocasionalmente, podríamos utilizar o aumentar la Información Personal que tenemos acerca de usted con información obtenido de terceros (p. ej., FitBit o Apple). Por ejemplo, podríamos utilizar tal información obtenida de terceros para confirmar información de contacto o financiera, para verificar elegibilidad o para comprender mejor sus intereses al asociar información demográfica a la información que usted haya brindado.

Recolectamos los siguientes tipos de información:

Información Personal que usted nos brinda

Recibimos y guardamos toda información que usted ingresa en nuestro Sitio o Aplicación Móvil, o que nos brinda a través de los Servicios, incluidos los servicios de cualquier tercero que lo conecten con nuestros Servicios (p. ej., FitBit o Apple). La Información Personal que recolectamos podría incluir datos tales como su nombre completo, sexo, número de teléfono celular, información acerca de sus tarjetas de crédito u otra información sobre pagos (si corresponde; es decir, en caso de participantes que paguen por su cuenta), su dirección de correo electrónico y la dirección de correo electrónico de sus contactos, sus domicilios postales personal y comercial, su dirección IP, información de su navegador, nombre de usuario, contraseña, cierta información médica (por ejemplo, estatura; peso, presión arterial; glucemia; afecciones médicas preexistentes; seguimiento de alimentación, sueño y/o actividad; e información sobre seguros), y toda otra información o datos que brinde al utilizar nuestro Sitio, Aplicación Móvil y/o Servicios. Usted puede elegir no brindarnos cierta información, pero eso podría tener como consecuencia nuestra incapacidad de brindarle acceso a varias de nuestras aplicaciones especiales o permitirle usarlas. El objetivo de Omada es utilizar la Información Personal que usted nos brinda para fines tales como la respuesta de preguntas y la comunicación con usted acerca de los productos y los servicios de la Empresa, lo cual incluye actualizaciones y nuevas aplicaciones.

NÓTESE: Al utilizar nuestros Servicios, usted presta su consentimiento y autoriza a Omada a divulgar que usted es elegible para los Servicios y participa en ellos (es decir, que cumple con los criterios clínicos para la inscripción en los Servicios, lo que puede identificar a aquellas personas con riesgo de sufrir determinadas enfermedades crónicas o que conviven con determinadas enfermedades crónicas, y que eligió a su entera discreción participar en ellos) a otros usuarios del Sitio, de la Aplicación Móvil y de los Servicios. Los usuarios, entre ellos, a título enunciativo y no limitativo, los administradores, asesores de salud y otros miembros autorizados del personal de Omada, así como los miembros de sus grupos de apoyo tendrán acceso a una variedad de Información Personal, tal como su nombre de usuario y foto asociados a su diagnóstico y/o a la razón de su participación en el programa. Además, dado que agrupamos a los participantes según ciertas características, los miembros de sus grupos de apoyo podrían ser sus compañeros de trabajo u otras personas que usted conozca.

Realizamos grandes esfuerzos por proteger su privacidad; sin embargo, no podemos controlar y renunciamos expresamente a toda responsabilidad sobre la posibilidad de que los usuarios utilicen o divulguen la información publicada o divulgada previamente o sobre la manera en que lo hagan. Si usted no presta su consentimiento para la divulgación de tal información, no deberá acceder al Sitio, a la Aplicación Móvil ni a los Servicios, ni utilizarlos. Los Servicios incluyen la capacidad de los usuarios de compartir Información Personal, inclusive información respecto de su estado médico. Toda información que usted decida brindar o subir a los Sitios de los grupos o la Aplicación Móvil, inclusive Información Personal acerca de su estado médico, podrá ser vista por su grupo, así como por asesores de salud, administradores y otros usuarios. Dado que su información podrá ser vista por otros usuarios del Sitio, de la Aplicación Móvil y de los Servicios, deberá brindar sólo la información que esté dispuesto a divulgar. Es posible que tenga la oportunidad de hablar por teléfono o por videochat en una teleconferencia de grupo. La participación en tales oportunidades no es obligatoria, pero en caso de que decida participar, deberá compartir sólo la información que esté dispuesto a compartir en tales foros adicionales.

Información personal recolectada en forma automática

Recibimos y guardamos ciertos tipos de información cada vez que usted interactúa con el Sitio y/o la Aplicación Móvil y/o utiliza los Servicios. Recibimos y registramos información automáticamente en nuestros registros de servidores a partir de su navegador, entre ellos, su dirección IP y la página que solicitó. Además, podríamos utilizar identificadores personales para reconocerlo cuando ingrese al Sitio por medio de un enlace externo, como un enlace que aparece en la página de un tercero o en un mensaje por correo electrónico generado por Omada que le sea presentado. Véase también nuestra sección de ¿Qué sucede con las Tecnologías de Seguimiento? a continuación. También utilizaremos su información para brindar servicios y apoyo a los clientes.

En general, nuestros Servicios recolectan automáticamente datos de uso, tales como la cantidad y la frecuencia de visitas al Sitio y a la Aplicación Móvil y a sus componentes, en forma similar a los índices de audiencia televisiva que indican cuánta gente vio un programa en particular. Sólo utilizamos estos datos en forma global, es decir, como medida estadística, y no de una manera que nos permita identificarlo personalmente (“Información Anonimizada”). Este tipo de datos globales nos permite calcular la frecuencia con la que los usuarios o clientes utilizan partes del Sitio, de la Aplicación Móvil o de los Servicios, para lograr que el Sitio, la Aplicación Móvil y los Servicios sean atractivos para la mayor cantidad de usuarios y clientes posible y mejorar así nuestros Servicios. Es posible que brindemos tales datos globales sin referencias personales a nuestros socios y/o clientes para identificar la manera en que nuestros usuarios utilizan nuestro Sitio, Aplicación Móvil y/o Servicios. Nuevamente, nunca divulgamos información a un socio o cliente de una manera en que se lo pueda identificar personalmente.

Puede configurar su navegador para que rechace o deshabilite estos métodos de recopilación de datos, pero, al hacerlo, es posible que cambie su experiencia con el Sitio, la Aplicación Móvil o los Servicios; se reduzcan determinados aspectos de la funcionalidad del Sitio o de la Aplicación Móvil; o dejen de funcionar determinadas funciones del Sitio, de la Aplicación Móvil o de los Servicios. El Sitio podría no reconocer las tecnologías antiseguimiento empleadas por su navegador o no responder a ellas.

Comunicaciones por correo electrónico

Frecuentemente recibimos una confirmación cuando usted abre un correo electrónico que le enviamos si su computadora admite esta clase de programas. Utilizamos esta confirmación para ayudarnos a lograr que los mensajes por correo electrónico sean más interesantes y útiles. También comparamos nuestra lista de clientes con listas recibidas de otras empresas, a fin de evitar el envío de mensajes innecesarios a nuestros clientes. Cuando usted reciba un mensaje nuestro por correo electrónico, podrá elegir no recibir mensajes adicionales por ese medio al seguir las instrucciones incluidas para la cancelación de su suscripción. No obstante, al elegir no recibir más comunicaciones por correo electrónico después de inscribirse en los Servicios, puede limitar los recordatorios del programa y otros contenidos y componentes valiosos del programa.

¿Qué sucede con las tecnologías de seguimiento? 

Además de la Información Personal u otro tipo de información que elija enviarnos a través del Sitio, de la Aplicación Móvil o de los Servicios, nosotros y nuestros proveedores terceros de servicios podemos emplear diversos recursos tecnológicos que almacenan o recopilan determinada información automáticamente (o pasivamente) cuando usted visita el Sitio, la Aplicación Móvil o los Servicios, o interactúa con ellos (“Información de Uso”). Esta Información de Uso se puede almacenar, o se puede acceder a ella, mediante tecnologías que pueden descargarse en su Dispositivo cada vez que visite el Sitio, la Aplicación Móvil o los Servicios, o interactúe con ellos. En la medida en que asociemos la Información de Uso con su Información Personal recopilada directamente de usted, la trataremos como Información Personal. Algunos ejemplos de Información de Uso incluyen: su dirección IP u otro identificador de dispositivo único (p. ej., un número que se le asigna automáticamente a su Dispositivo y se utiliza para acceder al Sitio, y que nuestras computadoras usan para identificar su Dispositivo), funcionalidades de su Dispositivo (p. ej., navegador, sistema operativo, información de la red móvil, etc.), las áreas que visita dentro del Sitio o de los Servicios y las actividades que realiza allí, la ubicación de su Dispositivo, las características de su Dispositivo y otros datos determinados relativos a su Dispositivo.

Podemos utilizar diversos métodos o tecnologías para almacenar o recopilar su Información de Uso, incluidas sus visitas a nuestro Sitio, Aplicación Móvil y Servicios, o sus interacciones con ellos (“Tecnologías de Seguimiento”). Podemos utilizar estas Tecnologías de Seguimiento con diversos fines, incluidos, a título ilustrativo, usos que se consideren necesarios o útiles para evaluar el rendimiento de nuestro Sitio, Aplicación Móvil y Servicios (por ejemplo, como parte de nuestras prácticas analíticas, o para mejorar nuestro Sitio, Aplicación Móvil y Servicios) o usos que se requieren para ofrecerle una funcionalidad mejorada al acceder a nuestro Sitio, Aplicación Móvil y Servicios (esto incluye identificarlo cuando inicia sesión en el Sitio o la Aplicación Móvil, o realizar un seguimiento de sus preferencias indicadas).

Las Tecnologías de Seguimiento pueden incluir las siguientes (y pueden incluir tecnologías y métodos posteriores que se desarrollen en el futuro y desempeñen una función similar):

Cookies. Las cookies son identificadores alfanuméricos que transferimos al disco rígido de su computadora a través de su navegador para permitir que nuestros sistemas reconozcan su navegador y nos indiquen la manera y los momentos en que las personas visitan las páginas de nuestro Sitio y cuántas personas lo hacen. Utilizamos cookies para mejorar las experiencias de los visitantes al comprender la manera en que ellos y los usuarios interactúan con nuestro Sitio y los navegan. Las cookies regulares, en general, se pueden deshabilitar o eliminar mediante herramientas que están disponibles en la mayoría de los navegadores comerciales y, en algunos casos, aunque no siempre, se pueden bloquear en lo sucesivo mediante la selección de determinadas opciones de configuración. Cada navegador que utilice deberá configurarse por separado, y los distintos navegadores ofrecen diferentes funcionalidades y opciones al respecto. Además, estas herramientas pueden no ser efectivas en relación con ciertos tipos de cookies (p. ej., cookies de Adobe Flash o HTML5). Tenga en cuenta que si deshabilita o elimina las cookies desde su Dispositivo, es posible que algunas partes de nuestro Sitio o Servicios no funcionen correctamente, y que cuando vuelva a visitar nuestro Sitio o Servicios, su capacidad para limitar las cookies dependerá de la configuración y las limitaciones de su navegador.

Podemos decidir publicar anuncios en el Sitio o la Aplicación Móvil. Tales anuncios podrán ser enviados a los usuarios por medio de nuestros socios de publicidad, que podrían utilizar cookies. Estas cookies le permiten al servidor de la publicidad reconocer su Dispositivo cada vez que le envíen un anuncio en la red para compilar información acerca de usted o de otros que utilicen su computadora. Tal información permite a las redes de publicidad, entre otras acciones, enviar anuncios dirigidos que consideren que lo interesarán en mayor medida. La presente Política de Privacidad se refiere sólo al uso de cookies por parte de la Empresa y no abarca el uso de cookies por parte de terceros (por ejemplo, anunciantes).

Scripts incrustados. Un script incrustado es un código de programación diseñado para recopilar información acerca de sus interacciones con el Sitio, la Aplicación Móvil y los Servicios, tal como los vínculos donde usted hace clic. El código se descarga temporalmente en su Dispositivo, permanece activo únicamente mientras usted está conectado al Sitio o a la Aplicación Móvil, y luego se desactiva o elimina.

Balizas web. Se pueden incluir pequeñas imágenes gráficas u otros códigos de programación web denominados “balizas web” (también conocidos como “GIF 1x1” o “GIF invisibles”) en las páginas y mensajes de nuestro Sitio, Aplicación Móvil y Servicios. Las balizas web pueden ser invisibles para usted, pero cualquier imagen electrónica u otros códigos de programación web insertados en una página o correo electrónico pueden actuar como balizas web. Las balizas web o tecnologías similares se pueden utilizar con numerosos fines, como contar las personas que visitan el Sitio, la Aplicación Móvil y los Servicios; controlar la manera en que los usuarios navegan por el Sitio, la Aplicación Móvil y los Servicios; contar cuántos correos electrónicos enviados se abrieron realmente; o contar cuántos artículos o vínculos particulares fueron vistos realmente.

Pueden existir otras Tecnologías de Seguimiento ahora o en el futuro que diseñemos y utilicemos nosotros en relación con el Sitio, la Aplicación Móvil y los Servicios. Asimismo, es posible que terceros utilicen las Tecnologías de Seguimiento con nuestro Sitio Web. Nosotros no controlamos esas Tecnologías de Seguimiento ni nos somos responsables de ellas. No obstante, usted acepta que podría encontrarse con Tecnologías de Seguimiento de terceros al usar el Sitio y los Servicios, y acepta que esta Política de Privacidad no se aplica a las Tecnologías de Seguimiento ni a las prácticas de dichos terceros. En estos casos, deberá controlar los sitios web de terceros para confirmar cómo se recopila y utiliza su información.

#### 3\. ¿QUÉ INFORMACIÓN PERSONAL COMPARTIMOS?

La Información Personal acerca de nuestros usuarios es parte integral de nuestra actividad comercial. No alquilaremos, venderemos ni compartiremos Información Personal acerca de usted con otras personas ni empresas no afiliadas, salvo para la provisión de Servicios, cuando tengamos su autorización para actuar de otro modo, según lo permita o exija de manera explícita la Notificación de HIPAA o según se permita o exija de manera explícita en virtud de la presente Política de Privacidad, incluidas las siguientes circunstancias:

Foros: Posiblemente brindemos acceso a su Información Personal a través del Sitio, de la Aplicación Móvil y/o de los Servicios (por ejemplo, foros de debate, salas de chat, páginas de perfil, carteleras, blogs, mensajes instantáneos, actividades, encuestas, juegos y otros foros de comunicación) (cada uno de los cuales se define como “Foro”) en los que publique información y materiales. Algunos de tales Foros se describen más específicamente a continuación. Nótese que toda información, texto e imágenes publicadas o divulgadas por el usuario en tales Foros o a través de ellos podría ser visto por el/los grupo/s del usuario, así como por nuestros asesores de salud y otros miembros autorizados del personal, administradores, personas que ingresen al Sitio o a la Aplicación Móvil y otros usuarios del Sitio o de la Aplicación Móvil. Específicamente, la Información Personal tal como la foto que ha subido y su nombre de usuario podría estar disponible para que la vean otros usuarios cuando usted realice publicaciones en tales Foros. La información respecto de sus actividades en tales Servicios también podría estar disponible para que la vean otros usuarios. (Por ejemplo, otros usuarios podrán ver una lista de todas las publicaciones que usted haya realizado en todos los Foros disponibles). Toda publicación que usted haya realizado en un Foro también podrá estar disponible para que la vean posteriormente usuarios del Sitio o de la Aplicación Móvil al desplazarse a publicaciones anteriores en el Foro. Le exhortamos a que ejerza prudencia y cautela al decidir divulgar su Información Personal, tal como su información médica u otra información a través de un Foro o de otra manera a través del Sitio.

Foros de debate y sales de chat: Podríamos brindarle funcionalidades para realizar publicaciones en nuestros foros de debate y permitirle ingresar a salas de chat y comunicarse con otros usuarios en las salas de chat. Nótese que si usted utiliza tales funcionalidades para comunicarse, su nombre / nombre de usuario se divulgará a todas las personas que ingresen a los foros de debate en el presente o en el futuro, así como a todos los usuarios que se encuentren en la sala de chat en ese momento. Recuerde que la información publicada en los foros de debate se convierte en información pública. Ejerza cautela al realizar publicaciones. Además, si un comentario que usted realiza en un foro de debate o en una sala de chat contiene Información Personal, no podremos controlar la manera en que la Información Personal sea utilizada o divulgada por otros usuarios del foro de debate o de la sala de chat. Le exhortamos a que ejerza prudencia y cautela al decidir si divulgar o no su Información Personal o cualquier otra información en todo comentario y/o mensaje y que sea precavido respecto de las personas a quienes envía tales comentarios y/o mensajes.

Servicios de mensajería: Podríamos brindarle funcionalidades para permitirle enviar mensajes, entre ellos, mensajes instantáneos, a otros usuarios a través del Sitio. Nótese que si usted utiliza tal funcionalidad para enviar tal tipo de mensaje a otro usuario, su nombre de usuario se divulgará a tal usuario, así como a los administradores. Además, si un mensaje que usted envía mediante tal funcionalidad contiene Información Personal, no podemos controlar la manera en que la Información Personal será utilizada o divulgada por el destinatario de su mensaje. Le exhortamos a que ejerza prudencia y cautela al decidir si divulgar o no su Información Personal, o cualquier otra información, en todo mensaje, y que sea precavido respecto de las personas a quienes envía tales mensajes.

EN CASO DE QUE USTED UTILICE LOS FOROS, FOROS DE DEBATE, SALAS DE CHAT Y SERVICIOS DE MENSAJERÍA, SEGÚN SE DESCRIBIÓ ANTES, NO SEREMOS RESPONSABLES DEL USO DE LA INFORMACIÓN POR PARTE DE OTRAS PERSONAS, INCLUIDA INFORMACIÓN PERSONAL DIVULGADA POR USTED O EN SU NOMBRE MEDIANTE SU SISTEMA EN DICHOS FOROS, FOROS DE DEBATE, SALAS DE CHAT Y SERVICIOS DE MENSAJERÍA. AL DIVULGAR SU INFORMACIÓN EN FOROS, FOROS DE DEBATE, SALAS DE CHAT Y SERVICIOS DE MENSAJERÍA, USTED RECONOCE Y ACEPTA TODO RIESGO Y DAÑO QUE PUEDA SURGIR DE LA DIVULGACIÓN DE DICHA INFORMACIÓN.

Perfiles de usuario: Podríamos brindarle funcionalidades para permitirle crear una página de perfil de usuario en la que podrá brindar datos sobre usted, entre ellos, a título enunciativo y no limitativo, su información médica, síntomas, tratamientos, así como sus opiniones acerca de su información médica o de usted mismo (“Presentaciones de Usuarios”, tal como se definen en nuestras Condiciones). También podría tener la capacidad de subir fotos, videos e historias a su página de perfil como parte de las Presentaciones de Usuarios. Las Presentaciones de Usuarios podrían exhibirse a otros usuarios (entre ellos, miembros de su/s grupo/s, que podrían ser de la misma implementación o afiliados de otra manera) para facilitar la interacción entre usuarios dentro de los Servicios. Se utilizan direcciones de correo electrónico para agregar nuevas Presentaciones de Usuarios a perfiles de usuarios y para comunicarse a través de Presentaciones de Usuarios. No divulgaremos directamente las direcciones de correo electrónico de los usuarios a otros usuarios, salvo en los casos en los que el usuario esté “conectado” a otro usuario por medio de la afiliación a un grupo compartido o una invitación, o si el usuario ha decidido incluir su dirección de correo electrónico en su Perfil de Usuario. Nótese que toda otra Presentación de Usuario que realice, inclusive de Información Personal, en su página de perfil o a través de ella podrá estar disponible para otros usuarios, la Empresa, la administración, moderadores y otro personal. Además, otros usuarios podrán publicar comentarios y ver comentarios publicados en su página de perfil.

Comunicación como respuesta a Presentaciones de Usuarios: Como parte del Sitio y de los Servicios, usted recibirá de nuestra parte mensajes por correo electrónico y otras comunicaciones relacionadas con sus Presentaciones de Usuario. Usted reconoce y acepta que al publicar tales Presentaciones de Usuario, podríamos enviarle mensajes por correo electrónico y otras comunicaciones (p. ej., mensajes en el teléfono o de texto) que determinemos según nuestro criterio exclusivo, en relación con sus Presentaciones de Usuario.

Empresas afiliadas que no controlamos: A fin de brindarle una experiencia óptima como usuario, tenemos previsto afiliarnos y trabajar estrechamente con una variedad de terceras empresas. En ciertas situaciones, tales empresas podrán venderle productos o servicios a través de los Sitios. En otras situaciones, podríamos brindarle servicios o vender productos junto con empresas afiliadas. Usted debería poder reconocer cuándo una empresa afiliada está asociada a sus operaciones, y a lo largo de las operaciones, compartiremos su Información Personal que esté relacionada con tales operaciones con tal empresa afiliada.

Representantes: Empleamos otras empresas y personas para que realicen tareas en nuestro nombre y necesitamos compartir su información con ellas a fin de brindarle productos y/o servicios. Sin autorización o consentimiento específicos, limitamos los derechos de nuestros representantes de utilizar Información Personal que compartimos con ellos a los que sean mínimamente necesarios para asistirnos. Por la presente, usted presta su consentimiento para que compartamos su Información Personal a los fines indicados previamente.

Recomendaciones: En ocasiones, podemos solicitarle o invitarlo a que les recomiende nuestros Servicios a miembros de su familia, colegas o amigos. En estos casos, es su responsabilidad asegurarse de que estas personas sean, efectivamente, miembros de su familia (relación de matrimonio, concubinato o padre/hijo) o personas con las que tenga una relación personal (frecuencia de la comunicación, intereses y opiniones en común, etc.). En resumen, le solicitamos que se limite a extender las invitaciones a personas de su círculo más cercano que puedan estar interesadas en nuestros Servicios. Les enviaremos un correo electrónico indicando que usted sugirió que podría interesarles probar nuestros Servicios. No volveremos a comunicarnos con ellos si no responden o si solicitan que no los contactemos nuevamente.

Ofertas promocionales: Nunca divulgaremos su información personal a otras empresas para sus fines promocionales, pero podríamos enviarle ofertas que promocionen los productos de otras empresas. Tales ofertas tendrán como objetivo beneficiarlo a usted, su salud o su experiencia con Omada. En caso de que no desee recibir tales ofertas, puede hacer clic en el enlace “Cancelar suscripción” incluido en los correos electrónicos o puede enviar un mensaje por correo electrónico con su solicitud a [privacy@omadahealth.com](mailto:privacy@omadahealth.com). Procesaremos su solicitud dentro de un plazo razonable, pero podrá recibir ofertas adicionales mientras estemos procesando su solicitud.

Transferencias comerciales: En algunos casos, podríamos elegir comprar o vender activos. En tales tipos de transacciones, la información de los clientes, inclusive la Información Personal acerca de los clientes, generalmente es uno de los activos comerciales que se transfieren. Además, en caso de la compra de la Empresa o sustancialmente de todos sus activos, o en el caso improbable de que la Empresa cierre o quiebre, la Información Personal será uno de los activos que se transferirá o que será adquirida por un tercero. Al continuar utilizando el Sitio, la Aplicación Móvil y los Servicios, usted reconoce que si vendemos o transferimos nuestra empresa (por ejemplo, mediante una adquisición) o un activo (por ejemplo, nuestra página web) a otra empresa, compartiremos su información personal con tal empresa y solicitaremos que tal empresa utilice y proteja su información personal conforme a la presente Política de Privacidad.

Patrocinadores y administradores terceros; según se exija por ley. Podremos, a nuestra entera discreción, compartir, transferir o divulgar de otro modo cierta parte de su Información Personal (p. ej., informes que contengan datos relativos a la inscripción, compromiso, permanencia y resultados) a su patrocinador o a los administradores terceros de su patrocinador (p. ej., proveedores de incentivos, administradores de bienestar, etc.) con fines relativos a operaciones de tratamiento, pago o atención médica, u otros fines que permitan o exijan las leyes, según se describe en más detalle en nuestra Notificación de HIPAA.

Protección de la Empresa y de otros: Podríamos divulgar Información Personal cuando consideremos de buena fe que tal divulgación es necesaria para cumplir con la ley, hacer cumplir o aplicar nuestras condiciones de uso y otros acuerdos o proteger los derechos, la propiedad o la seguridad de la Empresa, de nuestros empleados, de nuestros usuarios o de otros. Esto incluye el intercambio de información con otras empresas y organizaciones para la protección, detección o supresión de fraudes y la reducción del riesgo crediticio. De ser necesario, realizaremos todas las divulgaciones que se exijan por ley en relación con cualquier violación de la seguridad, confidencialidad o integridad de su Información Personal, incluidas, a título ilustrativo, violaciones de su “información personal” o “información médica” (según la definición de las leyes estaduales vigentes en materia de notificación de violaciones de la seguridad) no cifrada, almacenada electrónicamente. En la medida en que lo permita la legislación vigente, le divulgaremos tal información por medio de mensajes de correo electrónico o publicaciones destacadas en su perfil privado en el Sitio o la Aplicación Móvil con la mayor celeridad posible y sin demoras injustificadas, siempre y cuando concuerde con (a) las necesidades legítimas de las autoridades de orden público o (b) toda medida necesaria para determinar el alcance de la violación y restaurar la integridad razonable del sistema de datos.

Con su consentimiento: Salvo en la medida establecida previamente, se le informará cuando su Información Personal podría ser compartida con terceros y usted podrá controlar la divulgación de tal información.

Información anonimizada: Podremos crear Información Anonimizada a partir de la información que comparte con nosotros, incluida cualquier Información Personal, y utilizar dicha Información Anonimizada sin restricciones. Podemos, por ejemplo, compartir la Información Anonimizada con los patrocinadores que pagan su participación en los servicios (p. ej., informes que contengan datos relativos a la inscripción, compromiso, permanencia y resultados a fin de respaldar las métricas generales de éxito del programa) y con administradores terceros que trabajan con los patrocinadores para brindarle a usted determinados servicios (p. ej., proveedores de incentivos, administradores de bienestar, etc.). Insistimos, nunca divulgamos información global de ninguna manera en que se lo pueda identificar personalmente.

#### 4\. ¿MI INFORMACIÓN PERSONAL ESTÁ RESGUARDADA?

Empleamos medidas administrativas, físicas y técnicas que son estándar en la industria, diseñadas para resguardar y proteger la información que controlamos del acceso, uso y divulgación no autorizados. Además, cuando recolectemos, mantengamos, utilicemos, divulguemos o accedamos a su Información Personal, lo haremos mediante sistemas y procesos que cumplan con los requisitos de privacidad y seguridad de información establecidos por leyes federales y estaduales vigentes, entre ellas, a título enunciativo y no limitativo, la Ley HIPAA.

Además, su cuenta de usuario individual está protegida por una contraseña para su privacidad y seguridad. A fin de impedir el acceso no autorizado a su cuenta e Información Personal, le sugerimos que proteja su contraseña adecuadamente y limite el acceso a su computadora y a su navegador al cerrar sesión cuando haya terminado de acceder a su cuenta.

El Sitio y la Aplicación Móvil contienen enlaces a sitios web de terceros (Sitios Web de Terceros). Antes de usar los Sitios Web de Terceros o servicios relacionados, debe leer y aceptar las condiciones de uso y las políticas de privacidad de dichos sitios y/o servicios. No somos responsables de las políticas y/o prácticas de privacidad de ningún Sitio Web de Terceros, y no tenemos responsabilidad ni obligación alguna respecto de la disponibilidad, fiabilidad, contenido, funciones, rendimiento, exactitud, legalidad, idoneidad, servicios, materiales ni ningún otro aspecto de dichos Sitios Web de Terceros. La presente Política de Privacidad sólo se aplica a la información recolectada en nuestro Sitio o Aplicación Móvil, o mediante nuestros Servicios. Al acceder al Sitio Web de un Tercero, lo hace por su propia cuenta y riesgo, y comprende y acepta que es el único responsable de leer y comprender toda condición de uso y/o política de privacidad que se aplique a dichos Sitios Web de Terceros.

Nos empeñamos en proteger su información personal. Sin embargo, no podemos garantizar la seguridad y confidencialidad de la información que nos transmite o que recibimos mediante nuestro Sitio y Aplicación Móvil, por Internet o una conexión inalámbrica, incluido el correo electrónico, ni la idoneidad de las medidas que utilizamos para proteger tal información. El ingreso, acceso o uso no autorizados; las fallas de hardware o software y otros factores podrán poner en riesgo la seguridad de su información en cualquier momento. Esto se cumple especialmente en el caso de la información que nos transmite por correo electrónico o mensaje de texto, puesto que no tenemos ninguna manera de proteger esa información hasta que llega a nosotros. Los correos electrónicos y mensajes de texto, y las líneas de comunicación por donde viajan, no cuentan con las funciones de seguridad que poseen nuestro Sitio y Aplicación Móvil, y pueden no ser seguros. Asimismo, al descargar la Aplicación Móvil de una plataforma de distribución digital, como la App Store de Apple o Google Play (un “Proveedor de Aplicaciones Móviles”), el Proveedor de Aplicaciones Móviles y sus representantes pueden ser capaces de identificarlo como usuario de nuestros Servicios. Si usted tiene razones para creer que sus datos o interacciones con nosotros ya no están protegidos, podrá comunicarse con nosotros a la dirección de correo electrónico, dirección postal o al número telefónico indicados al final de la presente Política de Privacidad. Además, si tiene alguna pregunta respecto de la privacidad o de la seguridad de datos, no dude en comunicarse con la oficina identificada al final de la presente.

#### 5\. ¿A QUÉ INFORMACIÓN PERSONAL PUEDO ACCEDER Y CORREGIR?

Puede acceder a determinada información acerca de usted a fin de que pueda ver y, en ciertas situaciones, actualizar tal información. Esta lista podrá modificarse a medida que se modifiquen el Sitio y los Servicios.

  * Nombre real
  * Información de cuenta y de perfil de usuario (por ejemplo, apodo y foto)
  * Dirección de correo electrónico de usuario
  * Dirección postal de usuario
  * Número de teléfono celular de usuario
  * Nombre de usuario y contraseña
  * Preferencias de comunicación

Para ayudarnos a mantener su información actualizada y asegurarnos de que sea correcta, actualice su información si sufre algún cambio, o infórmenos al respecto de inmediato a la dirección [support@omadahealth.com](mailto:support@omadahealth.com) para que podamos realizar las modificaciones que correspondan.

#### 6\. ¿QUÉ OPCIONES TENGO RESPECTO DE MI INFORMACIÓN PERSONAL?

Según lo indicado previamente, usted siempre podrá optar por no divulgar información, aunque podrá ser necesaria para aprovechar ciertas aplicaciones del Sitio, de la Aplicación Móvil y de los Servicios.

Usted podrá agregar o actualizar ciertos datos en las páginas, tales como los indicados en la sección “¿A qué información personal puedo acceder y corregir?” precedente. Sin embargo, cuando actualiza información, frecuentemente mantenemos una copia de la información no modificada en nuestros registros.

Si desea que eliminemos sus registros de nuestro sistema, podrá solicitar la eliminación de su cuenta al enviarnos un mensaje por correo electrónico a [privacy@omadahealth.com](mailto:privacy@omadahealth.com). Nótese que parte de la información podrá permanecer en nuestros registros luego de la eliminación de su cuenta, inclusive toda información o registro que estemos obligados a mantener por ley. Procesaremos su solicitud dentro de un plazo razonable, pero nótese que usted podrá recibir comunicaciones y ofertas adicionales mientras estemos procesando su solicitud.

Si no desea recibir mensajes por correo electrónico ni otro tipo de correo, llamadas telefónicas ni mensajes de texto de nuestra parte, haga clic en el enlace “Cancelar suscripción” incluido en los correos electrónicos o indique tal preferencia al enviarnos un mensaje por correo electrónico a [privacy@omadahealth.com](mailto:privacy@omadahealth.com). Nótese que si no quiere recibir notificaciones legales de nuestra parte, tales como la presente Política de Privacidad, tales notificaciones legales seguirán rigiendo su uso del Sitio, de la Aplicación Móvil y de los Servicios, y usted es responsable de revisar tales notificaciones legales para informarse acerca de toda modificación. Procesaremos su solicitud en un plazo razonable, pero tenga en cuenta que podrá recibir correos electrónicos adicionales mientras tanto.

#### 7\. ¿CÓMO PROTEGEMOS LA INFORMACIÓN PERSONAL DE LOS NIÑOS?

Los Servicios no están dirigidos a niños. No permitimos ni solicitamos intencionalmente la participación independiente de personas menores a 18 años de edad en ninguno de los Servicios. No recolectamos intencionalmente Información Personal de niños. Si un padre o tutor tiene conocimiento de que su hijo nos ha brindado Información Personal, debe comunicarse con nosotros. Si recibimos información de que un usuario de los Servicios tiene menos de 18 años de edad y nos ha brindado Información Personal sin el consentimiento verificable de los padres, eliminaremos tal Información Personal de nuestros archivos.

#### 8\. MODIFICACIONES A LA PRESENTE POLÍTICA DE PRIVACIDAD

Al utilizar el Sitio, la Aplicación Móvil y los Servicios, usted acepta la Política de Privacidad actual y nuestras Condiciones, a las que se encuentra incorporada la presente Política de Privacidad. Nos reservamos el derecho, a nuestro criterio exclusivo, de modificar, suspender o cancelar los Servicios o de modificar la presente Política de Privacidad en cualquier momento. El uso de la información que recolectamos ahora se encuentra sujeto a la Política de Privacidad vigente en el momento en que se utiliza o divulga tal información. En caso de que realicemos cambios en la manera en que utilizamos la Información Personal, usted será informado mediante la publicación de un aviso en nuestro Sitio y/o un mensaje por correo electrónico. Al continuar accediendo a los Servicios o utilizándolos luego de que hayamos publicado una modificación o de que le hayamos enviado una notificación de la modificación, usted indica que acepta adherir a la Política de Privacidad modificada. En caso de que no considere aceptable la Política de Privacidad modificada, su único recurso es dejar de acceder al Sitio o a la Aplicación Móvil o dejar de utilizar los Servicios.

#### 9\. PREGUNTAS O INQUIETUDES

Si tiene preguntas, inquietudes o quejas relativas a la privacidad en nuestro Sitio o Aplicación Móvil, o si desea solicitar el acceso a su Información Personal o que se realicen correcciones en ella, comuníquese con nuestro Responsable de Privacidad:

Por correo electrónico: [privacy@omadahealth.com](mailto:privacy@omadahealth.com)

Por correo:  
Privacy Officer  
Omada Health, Inc.  
500 Sansome St., Suite 200  
San Francisco, CA 94111

Por teléfono: 415.484.7050

Haremos todo lo posible por responder sus preguntas, inquietudes, quejas y solicitudes en un plazo razonable.

Fecha de entrada en vigencia: 1 de febrero de 2017

* * *

### Privacy Policy (Canada)

Omada Health, Inc. (the “Company”) knows that you care about how your personal information is collected, used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. By visiting the [go.omadahealth.com](https://go.omadahealth.com/) website and domain name (and the other websites we own or operate, including, without limitation, [www.omadahealth.com](https://www.omadahealth.com/)) and any other linked pages, features, content, or related services offered from time to time by the Company in connection therewith (collectively, the “Site” as further defined in our Terms of Use (“Terms”)), using our mobile application (the “Mobile App”) or using any of our Services, you consent to this Privacy Policy and to our use and processing of Personal Information for the purposes set forth herein. Capitalized terms not defined in this Privacy Policy shall have the meanings set forth in our Terms, available at [go.omadahealth.com/terms-of-use](https://go.omadahealth.com/terms-of-use).

“Company” or the terms “we” or “us” or similar terms refer to Omada Health, Inc. “You” or “your” or similar terms refer to you as a user of our Services.

By accepting our Privacy Policy during registration, or by visiting and/or using the Site, the Mobile App or any of our Services, you expressly consent to our collection, use, disclosure and otherwise processing of your Personal Information (as defined below) in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

As used in this Privacy Policy, the terms “using” and “processing” information include, among other things, using cookies or embedded scripts on a computer, browser, laptop, tablet, mobile phone or other device (a “Device”), subjecting the information to statistical or other analysis, such as satisfaction surveys and benchmarking as well as quality assurance and training purposes, and using or handling information in any way, including without limitation collecting, storing, evaluating, modifying, deleting, using, combining, disclosing, and transferring information within our organization or among our affiliates within the United States or internationally, as well as using personal information to respond to user / applicant or sponsor (i.e., the entity or organization paying for your participation in our Services) requests and to provide the requested products and services.

Transfer of Information Abroad

By disclosing your Personal Information to us, you consent to your Personal Information being transferred outside of the jurisdiction of the country in which it may have been collected. If you are accessing our Services from outside the United States, please be advised that by your continued use of our Services, you consent to the transfer, processing and storage of your Personal Information outside of the jurisdiction of your country and to make use of Services governed by laws regarding the protection of personal information which may offer a different level of protection than that provided in your country.

#### 1\. WHAT DOES THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVER?

Personal Information – In General.

This Privacy Policy covers how we use and disclose personally identifiable information that we gather from you starting from the time that you initially access our Site, our Mobile App or use our Services. Personally identifiable information refers to any information about you that can be used to contact or identify you and information on your use or potential use of the Site, our Mobile App or our Services, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a personal profile, an email address or other contact information (collectively, “Personal Information”). Your privacy is important to us, and we are committed to carefully managing your Personal Information in connection with the Services that we provide. It is important for you to understand, however, that this policy does not apply to the practices of companies and / or websites or other third party services that we do not own or control, or to individuals that we do not employ or manage.

Personal Health Information.

We are dedicated to maintaining the privacy and integrity of your personal health information that we receive from you as part of your application for or participation in the Services (“PHI”). PHI is Personal) Information that we receive from you as part of your application for or participation in the our program that relates to (a) your past, present, or future physical or mental health or condition, (b) the provision of health care services to you, or (c) your past, present, or future payment for the provision of health care, which is created, received, transmitted, or maintained by the Company. This Privacy Policy describes how we protect your privacy as a visitor to, or general user of our Site, our Mobile App and Services. You have additional rights under federal and state law with respect to the access to, use, and disclosure of Personal Information that constitutes PHI.

This Privacy Policy only governs information collected on our Site, our Mobile App or through our Services. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies and / or Sites that we do not own or control, or to individuals that we do not employ or manage.

#### 2\. WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

We collect Personal Information you choose to provide us (e.g., through registrations, applications, use of the Services, surveys, and in connection with your inquiries), starting from the time that you initially access our Site, our Mobile App or use our Services. The information we gather from you enables us to administer your account, provide you with the Services, respond to your inquiries and send you communications regarding the Services and your access to and use of the same, obtain your feedback on our Site, our Mobile App and our Services, analyze user behavior and activity, personalize and improve our Services, conduct research activities and contact you about the services that we offer.

From time to time, we may use or augment the Personal Information we have about you with information obtained from third parties (e.g., FitBit or Apple). For example, we may use such third party information to confirm contact or financial information, to verify eligibility, or to better understand your interests by associating demographic information with the information you have provided.

We collect the following types of information:

Personal Information You Provide to Us.

We receive and store any information you enter on our Site, our Mobile App or provide to us through the Services, including any third party services that you connect with our Services (e.g., FitBit or Apple). Personal Information that we collect may include things like your full name, gender, mobile phone number, credit card and/or other payment information (if applicable – i.e., self-pay participants), your email address and the email address of your contacts, home and business postal addresses, IP address, browser information, username, password, certain health information (e.g., height, weight, blood pressure, blood glucose, pre-existing medical conditions, tracking of food, sleep and/or activity and insurance information), and any other information or data that you provide when using our Site, our Mobile App and/or our Services. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but that may result in our inability to provide you access to or use of many of our special features. Omada’s goal is to use the Personal Information you provide for such purposes as answering questions and communicating with you about the Company’s products and services, including updates and new features.

PLEASE NOTE: By using the Services, you consent to and authorize Omada to disclose your eligibility for and participation in the Services (i.e., you meet the clinical enrollment criteria for the Services, which may identify those individuals at risk for certain chronic diseases or living with certain chronic diseases and have elected at your own discretion to participate in the same) to the other users of the Site, the Mobile App and the Services. The users, including but not limited to administrators, health coaches and other authorized Omada personnel, and your fellow support group members will have access to a range of Personal Information such as your user name and picture, linking you to your diagnosis and/or reason for program participation. Moreover, as we group participants based on certain characteristics, fellow support group members may be co-workers or other acquaintances.

We take great efforts in protecting your privacy; however, we cannot control, and expressly disclaim any responsibility for, whether or how users will subsequently use or disclose posted or previously disclosed information. If you do not consent to the disclosure of this information, you should not access or use the Site, the Mobile App or the Services. The Services include the ability for users to share Personal Information, including information regarding your medical condition. Any information you choose to provide or upload to the group Sites or the Mobile App, including Personal Information about your medical condition, will be visible to your group, as well as health coaches, administrators, and other users. As your information will be viewable to the other users of the Site, the Mobile App and the Services, you should provide only the information you feel comfortable disclosing. There may be an opportunity to speak on the phone or via video chat in a group conference call. Participation in such opportunities is not mandatory, but should you choose to participate, you should share only as much information as you feel comfortable sharing in these additional forums.

Personal Information Collected Automatically.

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with the Site, the Mobile App and / or use the Services. We automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, and the page you requested. In addition, we may use personal identifiers to recognize you when you arrive at the Site via an external link, such as a link appearing on a third party site or in an Omada-generated email presented to you. See also our What About Tracking Technologies? section below. We will also use your information to provide customer service and support.

Generally, our Services automatically collect usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to the Site and Mobile App and its components, similar to TV ratings that indicate how many people watched a particular show. We only use this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, and not in a manner that would permit us to identify you personally (“De-identified Information”). This type of aggregate data enables us to figure out how often users or customers use parts of the Site, Mobile App or Services so that we can make the Site, Mobile App and Services as appealing to as many users and customers as possible and improve our Services. We may provide this de-identified, aggregate data to our partners and/or customers to identify how our users use our Site, Mobile App and/or Services. Again, we never disclose information to a partner or customer in a manner that would identify you personally, except with your consent or as expressly permitted under applicable privacy law.

You may set your browser to refuse or disable these data collection methods, but doing so may change your experience with the Site, the Mobile App or the Services, diminish certain aspects of the Site’s or Mobile App’s functionality or render certain features of the Site, the Mobile App or the Services inoperable. The Site may not recognize or respond to “do not track” technologies employed by your browser.

E-mail Communications.

We often receive a confirmation when you open an email from us if your computer supports this type of program. We use this confirmation to help us make emails more interesting and helpful. We also compare our customer list to lists received from other companies in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our customers. When you receive e-mail from us, you can opt out of receiving further e-mails by following the included instructions to unsubscribe. However, by opting out of further email communications after you enroll in the Services, you may limit program reminders and other valuable program content and components.

What About Tracking Technologies?

In addition to any Personal Information or other information that you choose to submit to us via the Site, Mobile App or Services, we and our third party service providers may use a variety of technologies that automatically (or passively) store or collect certain information when you visit or interact with the Site, Mobile App or Services (“Usage Information”). This Usage Information may be stored or accessed using technologies that may be downloaded to your Device whenever you visit or interact with the Site, Mobile App or Services. To the extent we associate Usage Information with your Personal Information that we collect directly from you, we will treat it as Personal Information. Examples of Usage Information include: your IP address or other unique device identifier (e.g., a number that is automatically assigned to your Device used to access the Site which our computers use to identify your Device), your Device’s functionality (e.g., browser, operating system, mobile network information, etc.), the areas within the Site or Services that you visit and your activities there, your Device location, your Device characteristics and certain other data regarding your Device.

We may use various methods or technologies to store or collect your Usage Information, including your visits to or interactions with our Site, Mobile App and Services (“Tracking Technologies”). We may use these Tracking Technologies for a variety of purposes, including but not limited to uses deemed to be necessary or useful to assess the performance of our Site, Mobile App and Services (including as part of our analytic practices or otherwise to improve our Site, Mobile App and Services) or uses required to offer you enhanced functionality when accessing our Site, Mobile App and Services (including identifying you when you sign in to the Site or the Mobile App or keeping track of your specified preferences).

Tracking Technologies that may include the following (and may include subsequent technologies and methods later developed which perform a similar function):

Cookies. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our Site are visited and by how many people. We use cookies to enhance visitors’ experiences by understanding how visitors and / or users engage with and navigate our Site. Regular cookies may generally be disabled or removed by tools that are available as part of most commercial browsers and in some but not all instances can be blocked in the future by selecting certain settings. Each browser that you use will need to be set separately, and different browsers offer different functionality and options in this regard. Also, these tools may not be effective with regard to certain types of cookies (e.g., Adobe Flash or HTML5 cookies). Please be aware that if you disable or remove cookies on your Device, some parts of our Site or Services may not function properly and when you revisit our Site or Services your ability to limit cookies is subject to your browser settings and limitations.

We may choose to serve ads on the Site or the Mobile App. These ads may be delivered to users by our advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your Device each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy refers only to the use of cookies by the Company and does not cover the use of cookies by any third parties (e.g., advertisers).

Embedded Scripts. An embedded script is programming code that is designed to collect information about your interactions with the Site, Mobile App and Services, such as the links that you click on. The code is temporarily downloaded onto your Device, is active only while you are connected to the Site or Mobile App, and is deactivated or deleted thereafter.

Web Beacons. Small graphic images or other web programming code called “web beacons” (also known as “1×1 GIFs” or “clear GIFs”) may be included in pages and messages of our Site, Mobile App and Services. Web beacons may be invisible to you, but any electronic image or other web programming code inserted into a page or e-mail can act as a web beacon. Web beacons or similar technologies may be used for a number of purposes, including to count visitors to the Site, Mobile App and Services, to monitor how users navigate the Site, the Mobile App and Services, to count how many sent e-mails were actually opened or to count how many particular articles or links were actually viewed.

There may be other Tracking Technologies now and later devised and used by us in connection with the Site, Mobile App and Services. Further, third parties may use Tracking Technologies with our Website. We do not control those Tracking Technologies, and we are not responsible for them. However, you consent to potentially encountering third party Tracking Technologies in connection with your use of the Site and Services and accept that this Privacy Policy does not apply to the Tracking Technologies or practices of such third parties. In such cases, you must check the third party websites to confirm how your information is collected and used.

#### 3\. HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

Your Personal Information will be used to render our services, including but not limited to:

  * The ability to access health information shared by you and others through our Services, augmented with information collected about you through authorized third parties (e.g., FitBit and Apple Watch) and build an online community related to your weight loss and health goals.
  * Access to other information about Company and our products and/or services through the various websites we own and operate, including, without limitation, the [go.omadahealth.com](https://go.omadahealth.com/) website and domain name, and any other features, content, or applications offered from time to time by Company in connection therewith.
  * The ability to interact with relevant Company personnel in a timely and effective manner from the time of initial application and throughout the course of program participation.
  * Providing you information and advice on Health-related products and services, treatment alternatives and any other information related to your condition.
  * The purposes identified in the following section.

#### 4\. WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE SHARE?

Personal Information about our users is an integral part of our business. We will not rent, sell or share your Personal Information with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide the Services, when we otherwise have your permission, and as expressly permitted or required under this Privacy Policy, including under the following circumstances:

Forums: We may make available your Personal Information through the Site, the Mobile App and/or the Services (for example, discussion boards, chat rooms, profile pages, bulletin boards, blogs, instant messaging, activities, polls, games and other communication forums) (each, a “Forum”) to which you post information and materials. Some of these Forums are described more specifically below. Please note that any information, text, and images posted or disclosed by the user on or through such Forums may be visible to the user’s group(s), as well as our health coaches and other authorized personnel, administrators, visitors to the Site or the Mobile App, and other users of the Site or the Mobile App. Specifically, Personal Information such as the picture you’ve uploaded and your screen name may be available for other users to view when you make a posting to such Forums. Information regarding your activities in such Services may also be available for view by other users (for example, other users may be able to view a list of all postings you have made in all available Forums.) Any postings you have made to a Forum may also be available for view later by users of the Site or the Mobile App by scrolling to older posts on the Forum. We urge you to exercise discretion and caution when deciding to disclose your Personal Information, such as your health information, or any other information, through a Forum or otherwise through the Site.

Discussion Boards and Chat Rooms: We may provide functionality to post on our discussion boards, and permit you to enter into chat rooms and communicate with other users in the chat rooms. Please note that if you use such functionalities to communicate, your name / screen name will be disclosed to all visitors to the discussion boards, present and future, as well as all users in the chat room at that time. Please remember that information posted to discussion boards becomes public information. Use caution when posting. Further, if a comment you make on the discussion board or in the chat room contains Personal Information, we cannot control how the Personal Information will be used or disclosed by the other users of the discussion board or chat room. We urge you to exercise discretion and caution when deciding to disclose your Personal Information, or any other information, in any comment and/or message, and to be careful about the people to whom you send such comments and/or messages.

Messaging Services: We may provide functionality to permit you to send messages, including instant messages, to other users through the Site. Please note that if you use such functionality to send such a message to another user, your screen name will be disclosed to that user, as well as administrators. Further, if a message you send using such functionality contains Personal Information, we cannot control how the Personal Information will be used or disclosed by the recipient of your message. We urge you to exercise discretion and caution when deciding to disclose your Personal Information, or any other information, in any message, and to be careful about the people to whom you send such messages.

IN THE CASE OF YOUR USE OF FORUMS, DISCUSSION BOARDS, CHAT ROOMS AND MESSAGING SERVICES, AS DESCRIBED ABOVE, WE ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE USE BY OTHERS OF ANY INFORMATION, INCLDUING PERSONAL INFORMATION, THAT IS DISCLOSED BY YOU OR ON YOUR BEHALF BY YOUR SYSTEM IN SUCH FORUMS, DISCUSSION BOARDS, CHAT ROOMS AND MESSAGING SERVICES. BY DISCLOSING ANY OF YOUR INFORMATION VIA FORUMS, DISCUSSION BOARDS, CHAT ROOMS AND MESSAGING SERVICES, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND ACCEPT ANY RISK AND DAMAGE ARISING FROM DISCLOSURE OF SUCH INFORMATION.

User Profiles: We may provide functionality to permit you to create a user profile page in which you may provide information about yourself, including, without limitation, your health information, symptoms, treatments, as well as your feelings about your health information and/or yourself (“User Submissions,” as further defined in our Terms). You may also be able to upload pictures, videos and stories to your profile page as part of the User Submissions. User Submissions may be displayed to other users (including members of your group(s), who may be from the same deployment or otherwise affiliated) to facilitate user interaction within the Services. Email addresses are used to add new User Submissions to user profiles and to communicate through User Submissions. Users’ email addresses will not be directly revealed to other users by us, except when the user is “connected” to another user via a shared group membership, or an invitation, or if the user has chosen to include their email address in their User Profile. Please note that any User Submissions you make, including Personal Information, on or through your profile page may be available for other users, the Company, administration, moderators, and other staff. Additionally, other users may be able to post comments and view posted comments on your profile page.

Communication in Response to User Submissions: As part of the Site and Services, you will receive from us email and other communication relating to your User Submissions. You acknowledge and agree that by posting such User Submissions, we may send you email and other communications (e.g., phone calls or text messages) that we determine, in our sole discretion, are related to your User Submissions, except to the extent provided by applicable law.

Affiliated Businesses We Do Not Control: In order to provide you with the optimal user experience, we anticipate that we may become affiliated and work closely with a variety of third party businesses. In certain situations, these businesses may sell products or services to you through the Site. In other situations, we may provide services, or sell products, jointly with affiliated businesses. You should be able to recognize when an affiliated business is associated with your transactions, and throughout the course of the transactions, we will share your Personal Information that is related to such transactions with that affiliated business.

Agents: We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products and/or services to you. For example, we may make disclosures to claim and obtain payment from your health insurer or other company that arranges or pays the cost of some or all of your healthcare. Without specific authorization and/or consent, we limit the rights of our agents to use Personal Information we share with them to that which is minimally necessary to assist us. You hereby consent to our sharing of Personal Information for the above purposes.

Referrals: From time to time, we may ask or invite you to refer our Services to family members, colleagues or friends. In these cases, it is your responsibility to ensure that these persons are indeed family members (marriage, common-law partnership or parent-child relationship) or people with whom you have a personal relationship (frequency of communication, sharing of interests, opinions, etc.). In short, we ask you to limit your invitations to people in your inner circle that may have an interest in our Services. We will send them an email saying that you have suggested that they may be interested to try our Services. We will not contact them again if they do not reply or if they request that we do not contact them again.

Promotional Offers: We will never disclose your personal information to other businesses for their marketing purposes, but we may send you offers that promote the products of other businesses to the extent permitted by applicable laws. These offers will be intended to benefit you, your health, or your Omada experience. If you do not wish to receive these offers, you can click the “unsubscribe” link contained within the emails or you can send an email with your request to [privacy@omadahealth.com](mailto:privacy@omadahealth.com). We will process your request within a reasonable time, but you may receive additional offers as we process your request.

Business Transfers: In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information, including Personal Information about customers, is typically one of the business assets that are transferred. Moreover, if the Company, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that the Company goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, Personal Information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. By continuing to use the Site, the Mobile App and the Services, you acknowledge that if we sell or transfer our business (e.g., through an acquisition) or an asset (e.g., our website) to another company, we will share your personal information with such company and will require such company to use and protect your personal information consistent with this Privacy Policy.

Your insurance company. We may use and disclose your Personal Information to your insurance company for purposes of billing and payment for our services offered to you. We may also disclose detailed information about your participation in our program to permit your insurance company to evaluate the efficacy of the program and run their wellness incentive program to your benefit.

Health care operations. We may use and disclose your PHI for our health care operations, which include internal administration and planning and various activities that improve the quality and cost effectiveness of our services. Examples are using information about you to improve quality of care, for disease management programs, patient satisfaction surveys, compiling medical information, de-identifying medical information and benchmarking.

Protection of the Company and Others: We may release Personal Information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to protect our rights and comply with the law; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or which is otherwise permitted by applicable laws ((e.g., emergency that threatens the life, health or security) This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations when it is reasonable to do so for the purposes of preventing, detecting or suppressing fraud that is likely to be committed.

Lawsuits and other legal disputes. We may use and disclose Personal Information to comply with law, including in responding to a court or administrative order, a subpoena, or a discovery request. We may also use and disclose your Personal Information to the extent permitted by law without your authorization, for example, to defend a lawsuit or arbitration.

Law enforcement officials. We may disclose your Personal Information to the police or other law enforcement officials as required or permitted by law: (1) in response to a court order, subpoena, warrant, summons or similar process; (2) to identify or locate a suspect, fugitive, material witness, or missing person; (3) about the victim of a crime if, under certain limited circumstances, we are unable to obtain the person’s agreement; (4) about a death we believe may be the result of a criminal conduct; (5) about criminal conduct at Omada; and (6) in emergency circumstances to report a crime; the location of the crime or victims; or the identity, description or location of the person who committed the crime.

Mandatory Breach Notification: If necessary, we will make all legally required disclosures of any breach of security safeguards, confidentiality, or integrity of your Personal Information, including, without limitation, breaches of your unencrypted, electronically stored, “personal information” or “personal health information” (as defined in applicable federal and provincial statutes on security breach notification) to the relevant organizations and government, as the case may be.

To the extent permitted by applicable laws, we will make such disclosures to you via email or conspicuous posting on your private profile on the Site or the Mobile App in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, insofar as consistent with (a) the legitimate needs of law enforcement, or (b) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system.

With Your Consent: If there are reasons we need to use your Personal Information that have not been described in the sections above, we will obtain your written permission. This permission is described as a written “authorization.” If you authorize us to use or disclose Personal Information about you, you may revoke that authorization in writing at any time. If you revoke your authorization, we will no longer use or disclose Personal Information about you for the reasons stated in your written authorization, except to the extent we have already acted in reliance on your authorization. You understand that we are unable to take back any disclosures we have already made with your permission, and we are required to retain our records of the care we provide to you.

Third-party Websites: The Site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site you should read the privacy policy published on that site. This Privacy Policy only governs information collected on our Site and Mobile App or through our Services.

Third-party Materials: The Services may allow you to display, use, include or make available content, data, information, applications or materials from third parties (“Third Party Materials”) or provide links to certain third party websites (“Third Party Websites”). For example, the Services may integrate and use a scale through technology provider BodyTrace. In such an event, before using these Services, you must agree to the BodyTrace: Terms of Use and BodyTrace: Privacy Policy.

When you allow the use of any Third Party Materials or access any Third Party Websites, you do so at your own risk, and you understand and agree that you are solely responsible for reading and understanding any terms of use and/or privacy policies that apply to such Third Party Materials or Third Party Websites. These Third Party Materials and Third Party Websites are not under Company’s control, and Company is not responsible or liable for the availability, reliability, content, functions, accuracy, legality, appropriateness, services, materials or any other aspect of such Third Party Materials or found through the use of any Third Party Websites that link to or from the Services or are otherwise referenced in the Services. Company is providing these Third Party Materials and links to Third Party Websites for your convenience, and you understand that Company does not have control over the content and performance of any Third Party Websites and Company is not responsible for the content and/or performance of any such Third Party Websites. The inclusion of any such Third Party Materials or links in the Services does not imply endorsement by Company or any association with the Third Party Website’s operators. Company also does not accept any responsibility for technical failures or for unauthorized access of user transmissions by any third parties.

The providers of Third Party Materials and Third Party Websites (each, a “Third Party Service Provider”) may collect and use certain information about you, as specified in their privacy policies and terms of use. Prior to using or providing any information to any Third Party Service Provider, you should review their privacy policy and terms of use. If you do not understand or do not agree to the terms of a Third Party Service Provider’s privacy policy and/or terms of use, you should not use the related third party services.

#### 5\. IS MY PERSONAL INFORMATION SECURE?

We employ industry standard administrative, physical, and technical measures designed to safeguard and protect information under our control from unauthorized access, use, and disclosure. In addition, when we collect, maintain, access, use, or disclose your Personal Information, we will do so using systems and processes consistent with information privacy and security requirements under applicable federal, state and provincial laws, including, without limitation, the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (“HIPAA”).

Furthermore, your individual user account is protected by a password for your privacy and security. To ensure that there is no unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information, we suggest that you safeguard your password appropriately and limit access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account.

The Site and the Mobile App contain links to third party websites (“Third Party Websites”). In such an event, before using the Third Party Websites or related services, you must review and accept the terms of use and privacy policies for those sites and/or services. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices of any Third Party Websites, and we are not responsible or liable for the availability, reliability, content, functions, performance, accuracy, legality, appropriateness, services, materials, or any other aspect of such Third Party Websites. This Privacy Policy only governs information collected on our Site, our Mobile App or through our Services. When you access any Third Party Websites, you do so at your own risk, and you understand and agree that you are solely responsible for reading and understanding any terms of use and/or privacy policies that apply to such Third Party Websites.

We exercise great care to protect your personal information. However, we cannot ensure or warrant the security and confidentiality of any information that you transmit to us or receive from us via the Services offered through our Site and Mobile App, by Internet or wireless connection, including email, or the appropriateness of the measures we use to safeguard such information. Unauthorized entry, access, or use; loss; hardware or software failure; and other factors, may compromise the security of your information at any time. This is especially true for any information that you transmit to us via email or text message, since we have no way of protecting that information until it reaches us. E-mail and text message and the communication lines they travel over do not have the security features that are built into our Site and Mobile App and may not be secure.

In addition, by downloading the Mobile App from a digital distribution platform such as the Apple App Store or Google Play (a “Mobile App Provider”), the Mobile App Provider and its agents may be able to identify you as a user of our Services. If you have reason to believe that your data or your interactions with us are no longer secure, you may contact us at the email address, mailing address or telephone number listed at the end of this Privacy Policy. In addition, if you have privacy or data security related questions, please feel free to contact the office identified at the end of this Privacy Policy.

#### 6\. WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION CAN I ACCESS AND CORRECT?

You can access certain information about you for the purpose of viewing, and in certain situations, updating that information. This list may change as the Site and Services change.

  * Real name
  * Account and user profile information (e.g., nickname and picture)
  * User email address
  * User mailing address
  * User mobile phone number
  * Username and password
  * Communication preferences

In order to help us maintain and ensure that your information is accurate and up to date, please update your information if it changes or inform us promptly at [support@omadahealth.com](mailto:support@omadahealth.com) so that we make the appropriate changes.

In any case, on written request and subject to a proof of identity, you may consult the Personal Information that we have collected, used or disclosed. You may also ask by writing that any amendments be made to your records if the information is inaccurate or incomplete, where applicable, as authorized or required by applicable laws.

#### 7\. WHAT CHOICES DO I HAVE REGARDING MY PERSONAL INFORMATION?

As stated previously, you can always opt not to disclose information, even though it may be needed to take advantage of certain features of the Site, the Mobile App and the Services.

You are able to add or update certain information on pages, such as those listed in the “What Personal Information Can I Access And Correct” section, above. When you update information, however, we often maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records.

If you would like us to remove your records from our system, you may request deletion of your account with us by sending e-mail to [privacy@omadahealth.com](mailto:privacy@omadahealth.com). Please note that some information may remain in our records after deletion of your account, including any information or records we are legally obligated to retain. We will process your request within a reasonable time, but please note that you may receive additional communications and offers as we process your request.

If you do not wish to receive email or other mail, phone calls or texts from us, please click on the “Unsubscribe” link contained in the emails or indicate this preference by emailing us at [privacy@omadahealth.com](mailto:privacy@omadahealth.com). Please note that if you do not want to receive legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Policy, those legal notices will still govern your use of the Site, Mobile App and Services, and you are responsible for reviewing such legal notices for changes. We will process your request within a reasonable time, but please note that you may receive additional emails as we process your request.

Detention and Retention of your Personal Information

Our servers are located in the United States of America. Your information will be retained for a period of 6 years after the end of the period during which Services are provided to you.

#### 8\. HOW DO WE PROTECT CHILDREN’S PERSONAL INFORMATION?

The Services are not directed to children. We do not knowingly allow or solicit anyone under the age of 18 to participate independently in any of the Services. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us. If we become aware that a user of the Services is under the age of 18 and has provided us with Personal Information without verifiable parental consent, we will delete such Personal Information from our files.

#### 9\. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

By using the Site, Mobile App and Services, you agree to the current Privacy Policy and our Terms, into which this Privacy Policy is incorporated. We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used or disclosed. If we make changes in the way we use Personal Information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our Site and/or sending you an email. By continuing to access or use the Services after we have posted a modification or have provided you with notice of a modification, you are indicating that you agree to be bound by the modified Privacy Policy. If the modified Privacy Policy is not acceptable to you, your only recourse is to cease accessing the Site or Mobile App and using the Services.

#### 10\. QUESTIONS OR CONCERNS

If you have any questions, concerns or complaints regarding privacy on our Site or Mobile App or if you want to make a request to access or correct your Personal Information, please contact our Privacy Officer at:

By email: [privacy@omadahealth.com](mailto:privacy@omadahealth.com)

By mail:  
Privacy Officer  
Omada Health, Inc.  
500 Sansome St., Suite 200  
San Francisco, CA 94111

By phone: 415.484.7050

We will make every effort to respond to your questions, concerns complaints and requests within a reasonable time.

Effective Date: February 1, 2017
